Historic Image Collection HIC
Stage
- Buildings and Offices - Story and Cobb
- Buildings and Offices - Suffridge Building
- Buildings and Offices - Sun Building
- Buildings and Offices - Swartzell, Rheem and Hensey
- Buildings and Offices - Tower Building
- Buildings and Offices - Transportation
- Buildings and Offices - Union Building
- Buildings and Offices - Union Trust Company
- Buildings and Offices - United States News Annex
- Buildings and Offices - Walker Building
- Buildings and Offices - Walker-Johnson Building
- Buildings and Offices - Wardman Building
- Buildings and Offices - Washington Building
- Buildings and Offices - Washington Gas
- Buildings and Offices - Washington Loan and Trust Company
- Buildings and Offices - Washington Post Buildings
- Buildings and Offices - Wilkins Building
- Buildings and Offices - Winder Building
- Buildings and Offices - Woodward Building
- Buildings and Offices - World Center Building
- Buildings and Offices - Wyatt Building
- Building Museum
- Bullets, Washington
- Bureau of Engraving and Printing
- Bureau of Standards
- Burnes Cottage
- Buses
- Business
- Buzzard's Point
- CandP Telephone
- Cabin John
- Canal Boats
- Canals
- Canals - Chesapeake and Ohio Canal
- Capitol, US
- Capitol, US - Art and Sculpture
- Capitol, US - Exterior
- Capitol, US - Grounds
- Capitol, US - Interior
- Capitol, US - Statuary Hall
- Capitol Bicycle Club
- Capitol Transit Company
- Capitol Plaza
- Car Barn
- Cars
- Carillons
- Carnegie Institution of Washington
- Cartoons - Political
- Cemeteries
- Cemeteries - General
- Cemeteries - Cedar Hill
- Cemeteries - Congressional
- Cemeteries - Fort Lincoln
- Cemeteries - Glenwood
- Cemeteries - Oak Hill
- Cemeteries - Rock Creek
- Cemeteries - Woodlawn
- Census Bureau
- Centennial Committee
- Center Market
- Chamber of Commerce, US
- Cherry Blossoms
- Chesapeake and Potomac Telephone Company
- Children
- Children's Homes
- Chinatown
- Chinese New Year
- Christmas and Christmas Tree, National
- Churches
- Churches - General
- Churches - 16th Street Universalist
- Churches - All Saints Episcopal
- Churches - All Souls Memorial Episcopal
- Churches - All Souls Unitarian
- Churches - Allen Becton Memorial
- Churches - AME Zion
- Churches - Anacostia Baptist
- Churches - Anacostia Methodist
- Churches - Annandale Methodist
- Churches - Annunciation Catholic, Church of the
- Churches - Asbury Methodist
- Churches - Ascension Episcopal
- Churches - Atonement Episcopal Diocesan Chapel
- Churches - Atonement Lutheran
- Churches - Augustana Lutheran
- Churches - Bethany Baptist
- Churches - Bethel Pentecostal Tabernacle
- Churches - Bible-Way
- Churches - Bradburn Memorial Methodist
- Churches - Bradbury Heights Methodist
- Churches - Bridge Street Presbyterian (Georgetown)
- Churches - Brookland Baptist
- Churches - Calvary Baptist
- Churches - Calvary Gospel
- Churches - Calvary Methodist
- Churches - Calvary Protestant
- Churches - Cathedral of St. Peter and St. Paul
- Churches - Centennial Baptist
- Churches - Chapel of the Holy Spirit (Episcopal)
- Churches - Chapel of the Redeemer (Episcopal)
- Churches - Chevy Chase Baptist
- Churches - Chevy Chase Methodist
- Churches - Chinese Christian
- Churches - Christ Baptist
- Churches - Christ Church (Alexandria, VA)
- Churches - Christ Church (Georgetown)
- Churches - Christ Church (Washington)
- Churches - Christ Lutheran
- Churches - Christian Baptist
- Churches - Church of Christ
- Churches - Church of God
- Churches - Church of God in Christ
- Churches - Church of Jesus Christ of Latter Day Saints Mormon
- Churches - Church of Our Father
- Churches - Church of Our Savior Episcopal
- Churches - Church of the Brethren
- Churches - Church of the Covenant Episcopal
- Churches - Church of the Covenant Presbyterian
- Churches - Church of the Epiphany Episcopal
- Churches - Church of the Holy Communion Episcopal
- Churches - Church of the Incarnation Lutheran
- Churches - Church of the Nativity (Catholic)
- Churches - Church of the Pilgrim Presbyterian
- Churches - Church of the Reformation (Lutheran)
- Churches - Cleveland Park Congregational
- Churches - Columbia Heights Christian
- Churches - Concordia Lutheran
- Churches - Congress Heights Baptist
- Churches - Congress Heights Methodist
- Churches - Disciples of Christ
- Churches - Douglas Memorial Methodist
- Churches - Downtown Baptist (Alexandria, VA)
- Churches - Dumbarton Avenue Methodist
- Churches - Dutch Reformed
- Churches - E Street Baptist
- Churches - Eastern Presbyterian
- Churches - Eldbrooke Methodist
- Churches - Emmanuel Episcopal
- Churches - Emory Methodist
- Churches - Epworth Methodist
- Churches - Falls Episcopal
- Churches - Fifteenth Street Presbyterian
- Churches - Fifth Baptist
- Churches - First Baptist
- Churches - First Church of Christian Science
- Churches - First Church of the Nazarene
- Churches - First Congregational
- Churches - First Evangelical and Reformed
- Churches - First Methodist Meeting House
- Churches - First Presbyterian
- Churches - First Unitarian
- Churches - Foundry Methodist Episcopal
- Churches - Fourth Church of Christ Scientist
- Churches - Full Gospel Tabernacle
- Churches - Galbraith A.M.E.Z.
- Churches - Garfield Christian Memorial
- Churches - Garoenia Spiritual Temple
- Churches - Georgetown Presbyterian
- Churches - Good Samaritan Community Church
- Churches - Gorsuch Methodist
- Churches - Gospel Mission
- Churches - Gospel Temple
- Churches - Grace Baptist
- Churches - Grace Episcopal
- Churches - Grace Evangelical Lutheran
- Churches - Greater New Hope Baptist
- Churches - Greek Church and Adventist Church
- Churches - H Street Christian
- Churches - Hamline Methodist
- Churches - Holy Comforter Catholic
- Churches - Holy Name Catholic
- Churches - Holy Rosary Catholic
- Churches - Holyland Spiritual Temple
- Churches - I Street Meeting House
- Churches - Immaculate Conception, Church of the (Catholic)
- Churches - Ingram Memorial Congregational
- Churches - Jehoush Holiness Spiritual
- Churches - Keller Memorial Lutheran
- Churches - Lewis Memorial Methodist
- Churches - Lincoln Memorial Congregational
- Churches - Lincoln Road Methodist
- Churches - Luther Place Memorial (Lutheran)
- Churches - Luther Rice Memorial Baptist
- Churches - Marvin Methodist
- Churches - McKendree Methodist Episcopal
- Churches - Methodist Meeting House
- Churches - Metropolitan A.M.E.
- Churches - Metropolitan Baptist
- Churches - Metropolitan Methodist Episcopal
- Churches - Minnesota Avenue Christian
- Churches - Most Blessed Sacrament, Shrine of the (Catholic)
- Churches - Mount Airy Baptist
- Churches - Mount Moriah Baptist
- Churches - Mount Pleasant Congregational
- Churches - Mount Pleasant Methodist Episcopal
- Churches - Mount Rainier Methodist
- Churches - Mount Vernon Place Methodist Episcopal
- Churches - National Baptist Memorial
- Churches - National City Christian
- Churches - National Memorial Church of God
- Churches - National Memorial Presbyterian
- Churches - National Shrine of the Immaculate Conception, Basilica of the
- Churches - Nativity and Resurrection Episcopal
- Churches - New Bethel Baptist
- Churches - New Jerusalem
- Churches - New York Avenue Presbyterian
- Churches - North Carolina Avenue Methodist
- Churches - Northminster Presbyterian
- Churches - Our Lady of Victory Catholic, Church of
- Churches - Pentecostal Holiness
- Churches - Petworth Baptist
- Churches - Pickney Memorial Episcopal
- Churches - Plymouth Congregational
- Churches - Potomac Heights Community
- Churches - Resurrection Episcopal
- Churches - Review and Herald Memorial Seventh Day Adventist
- Churches - Rhode Island Avenue Methodist
- Churches - River Road United Presbyterian
- Churches - Rock Creek Baptist
- Churches - Ryland Methodist
- Churches - Sacred Heart, Shrine of the (Catholic)
- Churches - Saint Agnes Episcopal
- Churches - Saint Alban's Episcopal
- Churches - Saint Aloysins' Catholic
- Churches - Saint Ann's Catholic
- Churches - Saint Anthony's Catholic
- Churches - Saint Augustine's Catholic
- Churches - Saint David's Episcopal
- Churches - Saint Dominic's Catholic
- Churches - Saint John's Episcopal (Georgetown)
- Churches - Saint John's Episcopal (Lafayette Square)
- Churches - Saint John's Episcopal (Maryland)
- Churches - Saint Joseph's Catholic
- Churches - Saint Margaret's Episcopal
- Churches - Saint Mark's Episcopal
- Churches - Saint Mark's and Incarnation Lutheran
- Churches - Saint Martin's Catholic
- Churches - Saint Mary's Catholic
- Churches - Saint Mary's Colored Episcopal
- Churches - Saint Mary's Episcopal Chapel
- Churches - Saint Mary's Lutheran
- Churches - Saint Matthew's Cathedral (Catholic)
- Churches - Saint Mathew's Episcopal
- Churches - Saint Matthew's Lutheran
- Churches - Saint Nicholas Russian Orthodox
- Churches - Saint Patrick's Catholic
- Churches - Saint Patrick's Episcopal
- Churches - Saint Paul's Catholic
- Churches - Saint Paul's Episcopal (Rock Creek)
- Churches - Saint Paul's Episcopal (Washington)
- Churches - Saint Paul's Lutheran
- Churches - Saint Paul's Methodist
- Churches - Saint Peter's Catholic
- Churches - Saint Stephen's Catholic
- Churches - Saint Stephen's Episcopal
- Churches - Saint Teresa's Catholic
- Churches - Saint Thomas Episcopal
- Churches - Saint Vincent de Paul Catholic
- Churches - Second Colored Baptist
- Churches - Sligo Seventh Day Adventist
- Churches - Society of Friends Meeting House
- Churches - South Bethany Baptist
- Churches - Southern Baptist
- Churches - Takoma Lutheran
- Churches - Takoma Park Baptist
- Churches - Temple Baptist
- Churches - Temple Church of God in Christ
- Churches - Trinity Episcopal
- Churches - Trinity Methodist Episcopal
- Churches - Trinity Spiritual
- Churches - Union Methodist
- Churches - United Brethren Memorial
- Churches - United House of Prayer
- Churches - Ursuline Sisters Catholic Chapel
- Churches - Washington National Cathedral
- Churches - Waugh Methodist
- Churches - Way Back to Pentecostal
- Churches - Wesley Methodist Episcopal
- Churches - Western Presbyterian
- Churches - Westmoreland Circle Congregational
- Churches - Wilson Memorial Methodist
- Churches - Woodbridge Pilgrim
- Churches - Zion Evangelical Lutheran
- Churches - Circles and Squares
- Circles and Squares - 12th Street Circle
- Circles and Squares - Dupont Circle
- Circles and Squares - Farragut Square
- Circles and Squares - Franklin Square
- Circles and Squares - Grant Circle
- Circles and Squares - Iowa Circle
- Circles and Squares - Judiciary Square
- Circles and Squares - Lafayette Square
- Circles and Squares - Logan Circle
- Circles and Squares - McPherson Square
- Circles and Squares - Pershing Square
- Circles and Squares - Scott Circle
- Circles and Squares - Sheridan Circle
- Circles and Squares - Sherman Square
- Circles and Squares - Thomas Circle
- Circles and Squares - Ward Circle
- Circles and Squares - Washington Circle
- Circles and Squares - Union Square
- City Hall (Superior Court of DC)
- City Planning
- Civil Defense
- Civil Rights
- Civil Service Commission
- Civil War
- Clean-Up Campaign
- Clothing
- Colleges and Universities
- Colleges and Universities - American University
- Colleges and Universities - Benjamin Franklin University
- Colleges and Universities - Catholic University
- Colleges and Universities - Chevy Chase College
- Colleges and Universities - College of Preachers
- Colleges and Universities - Columbian University
- Colleges and Universities - District of Columbia Teacher's College
- Colleges and Universities - Dumbarton College of the Holy Cross
- Colleges and Universities - Gallaudet College
- Colleges and Universities - George Washington University
- Colleges and Universities - Georgetown University
- Colleges and Universities - Howard University
- Colleges and Universities - Trinity College
- Colleges and Universities - Washington Missionary College
- Colleges and Universities - Wayland Seminary
- Colleges and Universities - Wesley Theological Seminary
- Columbia Heights
- Commerce Department
- Congress
- Constitution Hall
- Continental Hall
- Contests
- Corcoran House
- Corrections, Department of
- Cosmos Club
- Courthouse / Courts
- Custis-Lee Mansion
- Dams
  See: Canals - CandO Canal; See: Potomac River
- Daughters of the American Revolution (DAR)
- Days, Special
- DC Bar Association
- Demonstrations
- Depots
- Description
- District Building
- Drug Stores
- Dumbarton Oaks
- Dumbarton Oaks Conference
- Eastern Market
- Eisenhower Executive Office Building
- Elections
- Electric Chair
- Electricity
- Embassies
- Embassies - Austro-Hungary
- Embassies - Bolivia
- Embassies - British - See: Great Britain
- Embassies - Brazil
- Embassies - Canada
- Embassies - Chile
- Embassies - China
- Embassies - Columbia
- Embassies - Cuba
- Embassies - Czechoslovakia
- Embassies - Dominican Republic
- Embassies - Finland
- Embassies - France
- Embassies - Germany
- Embassies - Great Britain
- Embassies - Guatemala
- Embassies - Haiti
- Embassies - Honduras
- Embassies - India
- Embassies - Indonesia
- Embassies - Israel
- Embassies - Italy
- Embassies - Japan
- Embassies - Liberia
- Embassies - Norway
- Embassies - Pakistan
- Embassies - Panama
- Embassies - Peru
- Embassies - Russia
- Embassies - Soviet Union - See: Russia
- Embassies - Venezuela
- Embassies - Yugoslavia
- Engraving and Printing, Bureau of
- Ethnic Groups
- Executive Office Building
- Exhibitions
- Federal Aviation Agency
- Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI)
- Federal Reserve Board
- Federal Trade Commission
- Federal Triangle
- Ferries
- Fire Department
- Fires
- Fish Commission
- Fish Market
- Fish Wharf
- Floods
  See Also: Canals - CandO; See Also: Potomac River - Floods; See Also: Weather
- Flowers and Flower Shows
- Foggy Bottom
- Folger Shakespeare Library
- Food Stamps
- Ford's Theater
- Forts
- Fountains
- Franciscan Monastery
- Freer Gallery of Art
- Funerals
- Funerals - Dirksen, Everett
- Funerals - Eisenhower, Dwight D.
- Funerals - Emery, Mathew G.
- Funerals - Harding, Warren G.
- Funerals - Hazen, Melvin C.
- Funerals - Hoover, Herbert
- Funerals - Kennedy, John F.
- Funerals - Lincoln, Abraham
- Funerals - MacArthur, Douglas
- Funerals - McKinley, William
- Funerals - Roosevelt, Franklin D.
- Funerals - Sailors from the USS Maine
- Funerals - Stevenson, Adlai
- Funerals - Taft, Robert A.
- Funerals - Unknown
- Funerals - Unknown Soldier
- Funerals - Waite, Morrison
- Funerals - Walker, John G.
- Funerals - Washington, George
- Gallery Place
- Gambling
- Gardens
- 4th of July
- Accidents
- Adams Morgan
- Advertising
- Aerial Views
- Accidents
- Adams Morgan
- Advertising
- Aerial Views